[{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Throughput?","choices":[{"id":32,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":31,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":30,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":29,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Rate?","choices":[{"id":72,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":71,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":70,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":69,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jitter?","choices":[{"id":168,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":167,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":166,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":165,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Latency?","choices":[{"id":187,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":186,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":185,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":184,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interplay_Factors?","choices":[{"id":283,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":282,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":281,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":280,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bandwidth?","choices":[{"id":377,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":376,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":375,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":374,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Congession?","choices":[{"id":539,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":538,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":537,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":536,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept System_Security?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Multiplatform?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Active_Optical_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Hybrid?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Physical?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BOOTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASET?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Active_Hub?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Finger_protocol?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept OSI_Model?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Topology?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Advance_Direct_Connect?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept High_Interaction_Honeypots?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Packet_Switching?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept _ac?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASETX?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASET?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RDP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept MGCP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Silicon_Photo_Diode?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Direction_control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Connection_Control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Throughput?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Malicious_Software?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Star?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept OFDMA?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Distribution_Switch?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Framing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SNMP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept POP2?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Adaptive_Switching?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IP_Address?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Type_2?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Connectionless_Service?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Star_Ring?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Extreme_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Stream_Cipher?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Windows_2003?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Wireless?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Production_Honeypots?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Novel_Netware?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interception?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Port_Address?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Passive_Attacks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Direct_Fiber?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Circuit_Switching?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Voice?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept User_Datagram_Protocol?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Routing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SOAP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept DSSS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Apple_Share?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RTSP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Fram_Relay?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Single_Mode_Fiber?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Direct_DS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Rate?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Low_Interaction_Honeypots?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Partially_Connected?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Yahoo?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bridge?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept PHP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Translation?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cat6?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Wiretapping?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept POP1?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Format_String_Attack?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Type_1?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Application?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Firewall?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Token_Ring?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SNMPv1?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cyber_Attack?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RC5?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Smurf_Attack?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Segmentation_and_Reassembly?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SDM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Ethernet?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Internet_Protocol_Version_6?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Flooders?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Metamorphic_Virus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Class_E?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FTTC?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IMAP2?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Internet?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Router_Operating_System?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept VBR-RT?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Telnet?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Torjan_Horse?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Target_Based_IDS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Molniya?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept STS-48?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Apple_Filing_Protocol?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept CD?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept TLS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept VRP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Star_Mesh?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept G?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept VOIP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Statistical_Anomaly_Detection?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RADIUS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Arbitrated_DS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Radiating?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BACnet?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Gopher_Protocol?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Mesh?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Screened_Host_Firewall?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Zombie?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Audit_Record?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept PM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Circuit_Mode?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SSH.2?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FTTN?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept HTTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Extranet_VPN?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Transport?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bastion_Host?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SQL_Injection?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept CISCO_IOS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Access_Switch?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SFTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Radio_Repeaters?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Port_Scanner?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Twinaxial?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Linear_Automatic_Protection_Switching?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Live_TV?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Windows_2012?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Service_Point_Addressing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Pure_Honeypots?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FTTH?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Internet_Relay_Chat?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept X.25?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Broad_Band_Router?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Store_and_Forward?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Socket_Address?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Ring?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Distributed_Star?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Video?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Misuse_Detection?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Dynamic_Routing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jitter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Google?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Unidirectional_Gateway?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SDP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept r_sync?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Ethernet_Hub?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Replay?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RG6?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cat3?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Xerox_PARC?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FHSS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Internet_Protocol?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Virtual_Private_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Triaxial?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Transmission_Control_Protocol?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Transparent_Bridge?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Latency?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept NNTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Mozilla_Firefox?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Elliptical?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Communication_Media?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Circuit_Level_Gateway?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Buffer_Overflow?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SC-FDM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Root_Kit?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Google_Chrome?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept _a_OFDM_Waveform?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Wide_Area_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Modification_of_Message?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept STS-768?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Intrusion_Detection_System?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Time_Shifted_TV?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Shared_Fiber?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SNMPv3?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Screened_Twisted_Pair?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Parasitic_Virus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Local_Area_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bidirectional_Gateway?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Oliver_Heaviside?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Access_Control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Zero_Day_Exploit?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Biaxial?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept VG-Any_LAN?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Source_Route_Bridge?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Logic_Bomb?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Peer_to_Peer?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Downloaders?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept _b?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Hotmail?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Modification?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept JUNOS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Session?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASET4?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept H.323?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Distance_Vector_Routing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SNTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Archived_Gateway?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept P?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept LAN_Repeater?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Spoofing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept DOS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Flow_Control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept AES?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Edge_Router?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Low_Earth_Orbit?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SMTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Orginal_IMAP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Detection_Specific?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ARPANET?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Block_Cipher?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Gigabit_Ethernet?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept STS-24?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept _n?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Polymorphic_Virus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Worm?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept DNS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Windows_Server?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Anomaly_Detection?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Datagrams?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Polymorphic?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IETF?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Metamorphic?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Memory_Resident_Virus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Physical_Addressing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Multi_Exploit?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Packet_Fittering_Routers?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept NFS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept G?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Public_Key_Encryption?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept AAL?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Twisted_Ribbon_Cable?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Blowfish?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Repeater_Hub?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SDH?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Negative_Filter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Class_Fa?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Alcatel-Lucent?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept LDAP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interplay_Factors?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Stateful_Inspection_Forward?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IANA?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Protocol?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Multiplexing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept X?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cat5?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Dialog_Control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Transport_Vehicles?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Computer_Networks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":1,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":2,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":3,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":4,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":5,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Symmetrie_Encryption?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FTTB?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Release_of_Message_Content?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept eMail?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Satellites?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept _g?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RC4?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Scale?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Frames?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Windows_2008?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Backbone_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept MAC_Address?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Class_D?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Encryption?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Research_Honeypots?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept PPP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Coaxial_Cable?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Forwarding?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASEX?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Application_Based_IDS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Skype_Protocol?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FTTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Windows_2000?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Distributed_IDS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept PPTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Virtual_Networking?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Media_Access_Control_Sublayer?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SSH?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Geostationary?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ZyNOS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept POP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Rule_Based_Detection?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept DHCP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Core_Switch?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Intranet?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept WDM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Multiport_Hub?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IAB?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IDEA?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept STS-12?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept STS-1?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Personal_Area_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Server?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Packet?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Video_on_Demand?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Class_C?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Compression?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept CSS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Packet_Mode?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SSTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Backdoor?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Native?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Network_Hub?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SMB?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IPTV?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Positive_Filter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ExtremeXOS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RSA?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Internet_Explorer?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Wifi_Repeater?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept VPN?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept HTML?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Linear_Bus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Switch?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Dairy_Chairs?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Intranet_VPN?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Type_5?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Loaded_TP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept NetBIOS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Hash_and_Mac_Algebra?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bandwidth?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept TDM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Public_Key_Cryptography?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Modem?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Physical_Layer?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Opera?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Service_control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Security?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":1,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":2,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":3,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":4,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":5,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept DICT?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Guided_Media?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept QAM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Campus_Area_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Passive_Optical_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept STS-192?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept CMAC?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Twisted_Pair?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASEFX?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Spatial_OAM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Brouter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IRTF?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Connection_Oriented_Service?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Class_A?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IPSec?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Gmail?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Masquerade?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept HTTPS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Host_Based_IDS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Repeater?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASE2?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Data_Link?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept User_control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept AM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RIP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Networking_Hardware?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept L2TP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept _ad?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept CBR?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ISP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Class_F?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept r_login?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cells?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Multiport_Bridge?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Spammer_Programs?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Statistical_Multiplexing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Unidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Media_Access_Control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Screened_Shielded_Twisted_Pair?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Ultrafast_Spreading?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Fragment_Free?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept POP3?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Presentation?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Internet_Society?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept DTLS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Digital_Signature?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Youtube?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Optical_Fibre?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Virtual_Circuit?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Unshielded_Twisted_Pain?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept STS-3?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SIP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept MIME?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Extended_Star?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Fabrication?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Twitter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Gateway?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IMAP4?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Idle_Scan?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Semirigid?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Auto_Rooter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IP_Suite?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Metropolitan_Area_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept User_Plane?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RFC?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Stealth_Virus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ab?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Windows_for_Workgroup?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept THSS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Plastics?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASET2?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Application_Level_Gateway?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Permanent?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IEEE_802.11?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept URL?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SOCKS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SNMPv2?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cisco_Inc.?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Synchronazation_Gateway?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FTTX?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Fully_Connected?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Yahoo_Mail?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept World_Wide_Web?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept TFTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Radio_Frequency_Signals?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Honeypots?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept FTTD?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IMAP3?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Key_Loggers?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Link_State_Routing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASE5?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Multimode_Fiber?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Traffic_Analysis?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Translation_Bridge?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Higher_Layer_Protocols?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Zyxel?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bonded_TP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Performance?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":1,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Virus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IMAP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept MPPE?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept STUN?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ASP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Internet_Protocol_Version_4?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Tunnelling?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Boot_Sector_Virus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Data_Center_Switches?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept MC-SS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Home_Area_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Optical_Repeaters?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept DES?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Wireless_Router?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Tree?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SSB?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Availablity?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept WLAN?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jupiter_Networks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Behaviour_control?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Core_Router?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Application_Layer?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Synchronization?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Safari?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Network_Interface?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Logical_Addressing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Single_Homed_Bastion?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ISO_Standard?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interruption?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept HMAC?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Internet_Layer?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IAX?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cut_Through?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Subscriber_Edge_Router?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept MOS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cloud_Managed_Access_Switch?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Hub?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Transport_Layer?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Infrared?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept NAT?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Congession?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Class_B?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Extranet?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Storage_Area_Network?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Exploits?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept JSP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept URI?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Rigid_Line?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Distributed_Bus?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cat4?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept NCP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Network_Operating_System?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Variable_Bit_Rate?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Polarization_Multiplexing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Remote_access_VPN?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Confidentiality?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Scope?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":1,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":2,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":3,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":4,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Integrity?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Huawei?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IES?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Heap_Overflow?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Inter_Provider_Border_Router?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept IMAP2bis?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Network_Based_IDS?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Facebook?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Data?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept RTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Gnutella?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Router?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Dynamic_TDM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept NTP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept G?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Virtual_Path?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Point_to_Point?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept BASEF?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bit_Torrent?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Static_Routing?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Microwave?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SVOIP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Analog_Modulation?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ARP_Poisoning?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Active_Attacks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Shielded_Twisted_Pair?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Switched?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Management_Plane?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SCP?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ATM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Cryptography?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Hardline?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Routing_table?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept SM?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Control_Plane?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept ATM_Layer?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Application\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Data_Link\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RFC\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ATM_Layer is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Switched is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SVOIP is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Scope is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Infrared is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IP_Suite is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Flooders is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"LDAP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"CMAC is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SFTP is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDM is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"POP1 is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP2 is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FHSS is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDP is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDM is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"TLS is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTTN is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTP is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"POP1 is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP2 is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Gnutella is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Integrity is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Honeypots is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Permanent is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Brouter is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bandwidth is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Intranet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Telnet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Internet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Ethernet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BACnet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PHP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"HTTP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSH is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NFS is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NNTP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DTLS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DNS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DOS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"BASET2 is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASET4 is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASETX is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ARPANET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DTLS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DOS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DNS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DICT is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IPTV is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IETF is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDP is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDM is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDH is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAB is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IANA is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"POP1 is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PHP is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP2 is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PPP is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDH is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SSH is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PHP is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP2 is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PHP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IANA is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAB is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSTP is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CSS is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSB is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMB is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PPTP is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IETF is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IPTV is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"TDM is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"HTTP is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"HTML is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ZyNOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"JUNOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Network is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Direct_DS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NetBIOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DHCP is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IETF is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DICT is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HMAC is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"QAM is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"QAM is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IPTV is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IETF is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IRTF is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_B is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Plastics is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Cells is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_C is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_D is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_Fa is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_E is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Wireless is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_A is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"VOIP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RIP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"VOIP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SIP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MPPE is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MIME is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"TLS is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"THSS is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTTN is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTX is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"TFTP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNTP is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTN is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"STUN is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ASP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSTP is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SSH is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SSB is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IANA is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"AAL is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"WLAN is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HTML is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"HMAC is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAB is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IANA is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAX is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"JSP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NNTP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NCP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NTP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IP_Suite is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SVOIP is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SMB is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SM is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"}]